1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/icon-acount"))
13. setText(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
17. setText(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
21. click(findTestObject("WEB/Login/btn-sign in"))
25. click(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/icon-acount"))
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/verify-succes-acount-login"))
33. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. setText(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/field-search"), "Iphone 11")
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
45. custom.ProductHelper.addAnyAvailableProduct()
1. status = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
5. if (status == "PASSED")
2. saveScreenshot("FAILED")
1. try
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. screenshotPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().png
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. takeScreenshot(screenshotPath)
21. println("Screenshot saved : " + screenshotPath)
6. saveHtmlSource("FAILED")
1. try
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. htmlPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().html
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. html = getHtmlSource(OPTIONAL)
2. println("Failed to save HTML source: " + e.getMessage())
9. println(Test Case '$testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()' finished with status: $status)